Contact

Sylhet ssumoncd2017@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ marketersumon12 (LinkedIn) www.seoclerk.com/user/ seosumon12 (Portfolio) www.fiverr.com/marketersumon (Personal)

Top Skills

Al-Powered Performance Ads Certification

Telecommunications

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Languages

Bangla (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Digital Marketing
Digital Marketing
Al-Powered Performance Ads
Certification

Sumon Chandra Das

Digital Marketer at Nifty IT Solution | Social Media Marketer | Social Ads| Google Ads | Email Marketing | On-Page SEO(WordPress) | Local SEO | Youtube SEO | Keyword Research | Lead Generation | Sylhet, Bangladesh

Summary

Hi, This is Sumon. I'm a Digital Marketer with 4 Years of Experience in Digital Marketing, On Page SEO(WordPress), Google AdWords, Social Media Marketing, Email Marketing, Lead Generation & Content Building also have a Great Knowledge of Amazon FBA/Dropshipping. Successfully Increased Organic Revenue by 80% for an Array of Small and Medium Business Sectors. Especially Seasoned in eCommerce Marketing and Brand Building. Successfully Freelancer at Fiverr & SEOClerks Marketplaces. Currently Studying BSc Degree in CSE.

I Always Try To Provide My Best Services for Every Client. More Information Don't Hesitate to Contact me Directly. Thank You So Much for Being with Me.

Experience

Nifty IT Solution Ltd.

Digital Marketer

July 2023 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Booking Dei Founder July 2023 - Present (1 year 3 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh

Nifty Bookkeepers LLC Digital Marketer June 2023 - Present (1 year 4 months) United States

SEOClerks
Digital Marketing Consultant

January 2018 - Present (6 years 9 months)

United States

Fiverr
Digital Marketer
October 2020 - Present (4 years)

Picasa Limited
Digital Marketing Executive
November 2022 - August 2023 (10 months)
Dhaka, Bangladesh

Solution Flows
Chief of Digital Marketer
May 2020 - September 2022 (2 years 5 months)
United States

Genius Computer & Technology
Digital Marketing Trainer
March 2019 - January 2020 (11 months)

FAME- Academy School & College Teacher Assistant January 2017 - December 2019 (3 years)

Education

The International University of Scholars

Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering · (October 2021)

Sylhet Polytecnic Institute, Sylhet
Computer Science · (January 2016 - December 2020)